"If you want a warm butt,
pay for it yourself."
(Raj:)Well, maybe I will, old man.
(Bernadette:)I think that's enough wine for now.
I just keep thinking how cool it would be
if I called my mom...
(Leonard:)...and told her that I got tenure at CalTech.
- She'd be proud, huh?
Oh, very. Assuming she takes my call. Heh.
(Sheldon:)My primary concern
with being granted tenure...
(Sheldon:)...is living with an insanely jealous
roommate after the fact.
(Sheldon:)I might need to sleep with a gun
under my pillow. Or a chainsaw.
(Amy:)Or you take advantage of your newfound
economic stability and move out...
(Amy:)...buy a house, get married, start a family.
(Sheldon:)Or the chainsaw.
(Raj:)And I will return to New Delhi in triumph
atop a bejeweled white elephant.